A Guide to the Wallace Company Records, 1783-1975 (bulk 1875-1945)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Subject Files, 1783-1975., Extent: 40 boxes. (Box 23-62)
  - Bills of Lading, 1872 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Bills of Lading, 1873 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Bills of Lading, 1874 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bills of Lading, 1875 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Bills of Lading, 1876 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Bills of Lading, 1882 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Bills of Lading, 1883 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Bills of Lading, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Bills of Lading, 1885 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Bills of Lading, 1886 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bills of Lading, 1897 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Bills of Lading, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Bills Outstanding, 19122 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bills Payable, 1891-1892 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Biographical Skectch, 1902 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Blacksmith Work, 1885 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Blotters (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Bond, 1870 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Bond, 1891 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Bond Issue for Norfolk County Railroads, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Broadsides (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Broadstreet Mercantile Agency, 1894-1895 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Brown-Manly Plow Company (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Budd, Theodore H., 1942 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Building Specifications and Plans (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - J. H. Bunnell and Company, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Calculations re: Hauling Timber, Railroads, etc., 1886-1890 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Camp v. Lake Drummond Canal and Water Company (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Campaign for Treasurer, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - J. I. Case Plow Works, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Cattle Inventory, 1885 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cattle Memoranda, 1892 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Celery Sales, 1893-1895 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Census of Water Transportation, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Charlton-Davis Company, Inc., 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Chattel Property Inventories, 1885 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Chattel Property Inventories, 1886 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Chattel Property Inventories, 1887 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Chattel Property Inventories, 1888 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Chattel Property Inventories, 1889 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Christian Brotherhood (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Churchland Academy (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Clippings (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - J. H. Cofer - Account of Sales of Dover Corn Crop, 1906 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Coker's Pedigreed Seed Company, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Commercial Exchange Bank, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Cooke, H. D., 1886-1889 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Coppersmith and Company, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Corn Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Corn Purchased, 1896 (January-February) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Corprew, Wilson (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
  - County Warrants (Payments), 1871-1876 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Cranberries (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Crop Reports Sent to Department of Agriculture, 1888-1894 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Crop Rotation Plan, 1883 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Culvert Under Canal, 1898 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Daniels, John T., 1885 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Darden Rental Contract, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Deed Abstracts (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Deeds, 1808-1820 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Deeds, 1830-1839 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Deeds, 1840-1849 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Deeds, 1850-1859 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Deeds, 1860-1869 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Deeds, 1870-1879 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Deeds, 1880-1889 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Deeds, 1890-1899 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Deeds, 1910-1919 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Deeds, 1920-1929 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Deeds, 1930-1939 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Defender Photo Supply Company, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Diary, 9 May - 4 June 1975 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Albert Dickinson Company (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Dismal Swamp Canal Company - Superintendent's Report, 1808-1820 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Dismal Swamp Forest Fire Control Project, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Dismal Swamp Inquiry, 1897 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Agreements (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Lists of Swamps (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Option (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Telegrams (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (May-June) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (July) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (August) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (September 1-15) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (September 16-30) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (October) (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (November) (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1895 (December) (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1896 (May-June) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1896 (July-August) (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1896 (September-October) (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1896 (November-December) (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Dismal Swamp Land Company - Thomas Watson Correspondence, 1897 (January) (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Dover Farm Boundaries, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Dover Farm - Facts and Figures (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Dover Farm - Federal Land Bank - Inactive (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - Dover Farm - History, 1917-1936 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dover Farm Production, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Dover Farm - Receipts and Disbursements, 1936-1939 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Dover Pay Roll, 1889-1890 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Dover Potato Crop (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Dover Records, 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Dover Shipments, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Drawing and Painting Exercises (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Dredging Permission to the United States Government, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Eason, Joe (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - "An Eastertide Motor Trip" by Charles A. Stewart, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Edmonds, Henry F. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Election, 1892 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Election, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Estate of George T. Wallace, Jr. (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Estate of John G. Wallace (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Estate of John G. Wallace II (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
  - Estate of C. W. Wickins (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Estimated Costs of Machine-Made Shingles, Staves, etc. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Etheridge, Dr. H. S. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Fairbanks, Morse and Company, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Falling Spring Lime and Marl Company, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Federal Land Bank - Dover Farm (Box 31, Folder 11-13)
  - Federal Land Bank - Dover Farm (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - Federal Land Bank - Glencoe Farm (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
  - Federal Land Bank of Baltimore (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Fee Bills - Clerk of Court (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Feed - Weights, Mixtures, Costs, etc. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Fertilizer Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
  - Filling Station Plans and Specifications (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Fire Insurance (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Fire Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - A. C. Fisher, 1895 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Florida Papers (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Foreman, C. T. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Freight Bills (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - S. H. and E. H. Frost, 1895 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Funeral of Veronica M. Wallace, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Garden Lot, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Gas Oven/Range (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Gates County Swamp Lands (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly (Box 33, Folder 4-7)
  - Germania Fire Insurance Company, 1885 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Glencoe and Dover - Receipts and Disbursements, 1932-1934 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Glencoe - Ditching, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Glencoe Wheat and Rye Certification, 1942-1944 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Goiner, M. M., 1895-1896 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Gramophone (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Gray Motor Company, 1916 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Greenville Land and Lumber Company (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Guaranty Title and Trust Company Loan, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Guide Printing and Publishing Company, 1894-1896 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Hall's Universal Fencing Machine, 1876 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Hands' Accounts (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Hands' Accounts - Frying Pan, 1885 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Hands' Accounts - Frying Pan, 1886 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Hands' Accounts - Frying Pan, 1887 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Hands' Accounts Settlements (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Hands Who Are Good (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Hanson, Christen - Receipts, 1885 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Harrisons' Nurseries, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Hartford Fire Insurance Company, 1945-1950 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Hollins Institute (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Home Fire and Marine Insurance Company, 1932-1933 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Home Floor Plans and Specifications, 1888 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Home Movies (3 DVD's) (Box 59, Folder n/a)
  - Horse Pedigrees (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1894 (February-May) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1894 (June-August) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1894 (September-December) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1895 (January-April) (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1895 (May-August) (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1895 (October-December) (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1896 (January-May) (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1896 (June-December) (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1897 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1898-1899 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1904 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1905 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1906 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - House Ticket Charges, 1907-1908 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - J. W. Hunter and Company, 1896-1897 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Inspection Certificates, 1888 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Insurance (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Insurance Company of North America (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Invader Oil and Refining Company, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Invitations (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Irish Potatoes (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Jacobs and Company (Insurance) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Jeffers, A. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1885 (January-April) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1885 (May-August) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1885 (September-November) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1885 (December) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1886 (January-June) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1886 (July-December) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, C. R., 1890 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, C. R. - Accounts, 1893-1899 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, C. R. - Expenses, 1888 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, C. R. - Expenses, 1889 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - King Washing Machine Company, 1871-1872 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Kingsland and Ferguson, 1886 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Kinsman, H. H., 1887 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Kirkpatrick and Company, 1871-1875 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Kleinberg Female Seminary, 1896 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Kryocide (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Lake Drummond Water and Canal Company (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Land Entries, 1880 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Land Grants and Patents (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Landowners Fronting Dismal Swamp Canal, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Lands of George T. Wallace Sold (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lands Sold for Taxes, 1873-1875 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Life Insurance Cost Comparisons, 1883-1889 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Lighter Loads - Coal, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1874-1885 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1889 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1892 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1893 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Lighter Loads - Memoranda, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 17-18)
  - Lighter Repairs (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Lindsay, A. H., 1877 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Livestock Memoranda, 1885 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Lumber at Gilmerton, 1878-1880 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lumber Inventory, 1885 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lumber Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
  - Lumber Used in Building Culvert Under Dismal Swamp Canal, 1881 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - R, G. Lyle, 1895 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Magruder, Julia M. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Markens and Biefeld (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Marsden Livestock Food Company Prospectus, 1896 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Marshall, A. N. - Towing Receipts, 1893 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - McCoy, William (Sharecropping Agreement), 1934 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - McManus, P. - Accounts (Box 37, Folder 12-13)
  - McManus, P. - Merchandise Orders, 1896 (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
  - McManus, P. - Shipping Receipts (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 17-19)
  - Memoranda About Horses (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum Book (George T. Wallace) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Service for Jefferson Davis, 1889 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1905 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1906 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1907 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1909 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Merchandise Inventories (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Merchandise Posted to Accounts in Hands Book, 1890 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Merchandise Posted to Accounts in Petty Ledger, 1891 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Merchandise Posted to Accounts in Petty Ledger, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1893-1894 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1897-1898 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1898-1899 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1899-1900 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1900-1901 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1901-1902 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1902-1903 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1903 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1904 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1905 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1906 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1907 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1908 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Merchants and Farmers Bank, 1934 (Glencoe) (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Minutes (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
  - Money Point Property, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Morris Plan - Bank of Virginia (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Motor Vehicles Tax Refund (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
  - Mutual Fire Insurance Association (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Mutual Reserve Fund Life Association (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Mutual Reserve Fund Life Association (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - National Bank of Commerce (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - New York City Tourism Information, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - New York, Philadelphia and Norfolk Railroad Company (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - John Nix and Company, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Norfolk and Carolina Railroad Company (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk and Carolina Telephone and Telegraph Company (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
  - Norfolk and Ouray Mining Company, 1881 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Norfolk National Bank (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Norfolk, Wilmington and Charleston Railroad Company (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Northwest River Water Program - Chesapeake, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 14-16)
  - Northwest River Water Program - Chesapeake, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Notes Due, 1893 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Notes Due, 1895 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Notes Due, 1896 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Notes Due, 1897 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Notes Due, 1902-1903 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Notes Due, 1903-1904 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Notes Due, 1904-1905 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Notes Due, 1905-1906 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Notes Due, 1906-1907 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Notes Due, 1907-1908 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Nottingham and Wrenn Company, 1897 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Obituary of George T. Wallace, 1889 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Old, William W. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Orchard (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Orders - Butler Brothers, 1910-1912 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Orders - John F. Foster, 1911-1912 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Orders - International Tailoring Company, 1910-1913 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Orders - Edward E. Strauss and Company, 1911-1912 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Orders - Miscellaneous, 1910-1913 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Parrish, T. K. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Patent - Plow Attachments, Traffic Signal (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Pay Tickets for Hands, 1898-1899 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Pearson, Allen and Company, 1870-1872 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Peat (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Pension - Butt, Martha (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Pension - Scott, Joseph (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Perry's Steam Packet Line (Box 43, Folder 7-9)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1875 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1879 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1880 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1881 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1882 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1883 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1884 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1885 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1886 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1888 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1889 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1890 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1891 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1892 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Personal Property Interrogatories, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Phillips and Sons (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Phone Messages, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Photography (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Piedmont and Arlington Life Insurance Company (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Max Pincus and Company, 1904 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Piston Research Corporation (Box 43, Folder 30-32)
  - Plymouth Swamp, 1876 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Political (Darden) (Box 43, Folder 34-35)
  - Political (Humpfries/Hand) (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Political Notes (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Pooled Stock Resolutions and Agreement (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Poor and Exemption Law, 1873 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Portsmouth and Norfolk County Association of Confederate Veterans - Blank Application Forms (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Postcard (Real Photo) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Post Office, Wallaceton (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Potato Memoranda (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Potato Sales Telegrams, 1894 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Potato Shipment Receipts, 1895-1896 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Potato Tickets (Box 44, Folder 9-10)
  - Potatoes Dug and Shipped, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Powers of Attorney (Blank Forms) (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Prayers, Sermons (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Prescriptions (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Price Lists, Catalogs (Box 44, Folder 15-16)
  - Producers' Price Current, 1895 (June-July) (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Production Credit Association (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Production Loan Application, 1934-1935 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Promissory Notes, 1891-1892 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Promissory Notes (Bryant), 1898 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Provident Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Proxies (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Purchases of Merchandise (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Rafting Equipment (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Ration Papers (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Holdings and Values (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Receipts (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Recipes (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Redfield and Son, 1895 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Reinterment of Jefferson Davis, 1893 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Republican Party, 1892 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Republican Party, 1894 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Republican Party, 1898 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Rice, B. S., 1885 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accomodation Notes, 1881 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (March-May) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (June) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (July) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (August) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (September) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (October) (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (November) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1885 (December) (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (January) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (February) (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (March) (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (April) (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (May) (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (June) (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (July) (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (August) (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (September) (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (October) (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (November) (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1886 (December) (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Accounts, 1890-1899 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Agreements (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Bills of Lading, 1885 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Bills of Lading, 1886 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Correspondence, 1874-1877 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Deed, 1875 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Estimates, Costs, Profits, etc. (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Fire, 1884 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Inventories, Assets, etc. (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Lighter Memoranda (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Richmond Cedar Works - Lists of Notes, 1876-1877 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Risley, Joseph H., 1884-1885 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Roache, M. E., 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Roberts and Williams Company, 1895 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - John L. Roper and Company (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Roughton, Joseph, 1885 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Royal Arcanum of Virginia (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Royal Arcanum Assessments (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Salem Academy and College (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Salisbury Manufacturing Company, 1898 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Sawyer, Otho (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - School Exercises - John G. Wallace III (Box 47, Folder 11-12)
  - School Exercises - Mildred Wallace (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Seaboard Citizens National Bank, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Seaboard Citizens National Bank, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Seaboard Citizens National Bank, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 3)